<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[25]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[DRESERIS,]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[Grazina]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[1969-12-31 00:00:00]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2016-06-12 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[1969-12-31 19:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2016-06-13 13:51:19]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2016-06-13 13:51:19]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[DRESERIS, Grazina Passed away peacefully on June 12, 2016 at the Hamilton General Hospital surrounded by her family. Beloved wife to Vladas for 68 years. Dear mother of Petras, and Leonas. Loving grandmother to Adomas (Julia), Maika (Stève), Natalija, and Ema, and great grandmother to Éva, Lucie, Mila, Noah, and Lucas. Friends may call at the MARLATT FUNERAL HOME, 615 Main Street East, Hamilton on Thursday, June 16th from 6-8 p.m. Rosary at 7 p.m. A Funeral Mass will be held at Our Lady Of Mercy Lithuanian Parish, 58 Dundurn Street North, Hamilton on Friday, June 17th at 10 a.m. Interment to follow at St. John's Lithuanian Cemetery, Mississauga. Donations may be made to Our Lady of Mercy Lithuanian Parish. Online condolences may be made at www.marlattfhhamilton.com]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[50892e126eef9e522a7cee136e3a3f1f.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[1969-12-31 00:00:00]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[2016-06-18 00:00:00]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[324]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[DICK,]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[Barbara Ann (nee Whyte)]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2016-06-27 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[1969-12-31 19:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:11:42]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:11:42]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[Barbara Ann DICK (nee Whyte)
DICK, Barbara Ann (nee Whyte) Barbara Dick was born in Ottawa March 13, 1939 to the late George and Margaret (nee Lawson) Whyte. After a debilitating battle with Alzheimer's, Barbara passed away at the Errinrung Long Term Residence, Thornbury, on June 27, 2016. Barbara will be profoundly missed by John Dick, her husband of 54 years, and her children Gillian Rowan (Vince Wruck), Hugh (Ilona Onodi), and Allison Dick. She will always be fondly remembered by her loving grandchildren Levi and Reuben Rowan. Barbara was predeceased by her dear sister Janet Wray. She was a loving sister-in-law to Janet's husband, Bob Wray, and to Gordon and Leny Dick (John's brother and sister-in-law). Her memory will be cherished by many nieces, nephews and friends. In 1946, Barbara's family moved from Ottawa to Montreal where she completed her primary and secondary education with distinction. Barbara obtained her Teaching Certification at the MacDonald Campus of McGill University and taught primary grades for nine years for the West Island School Commission in Montreal. Once Barbara's children were in school she returned to her Teaching career at the Halton Board of Education in Burlington by first completing a Bachelor of Arts Degree at McMaster University, graduating with first class honours and winning the Sociology prize. Barbara's thirst for knowledge continued and she obtained a Bachelor of Education from York University as well as numerous other education courses. Barbara's passion in life was her family, occupying much of her daily thoughts and conversations. She satisfied her curiosity for the world at large and other cultures through reading a wide variety of publications and through travel. In lieu of flowers donations to the Alzheimer Society - Grey Bruce (http://www.alzheimer.ca/greybruce) would be appreciated.]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[9a55b86f6532e217aeed82430a1945b1.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[325]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[ELLIS,]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[Charles Reginald]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2016-06-28 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[1969-12-31 19:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:12:19]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:12:19]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[Charles Reginald ELLIS
ELLIS, Charles Reginald Peacefully on June 28, 2016, God called Charlie home, in his 83rd year. Beloved husband of Diane. He leaves to mourn, daughters Deborah (Todd) and Diane (Sam). Loving grandfather of Travis, Aria, Meredith, Colin, Amanda and Gillian. Pre- deceased by his cherished wife Beverley, son Paul and Jennifer Anne Hide. Charlie proudly served 36 years on the Hamilton Fire Department and enjoyed 26 years of retirement. A private family visitation will take place at CRESMOUNT FUNERAL HOME, 322 Fennell Ave. E., on Thursday, June 30 from 12 p.m. until time of service at 1 p.m. in the chapel. Interment to follow at Woodland Cemetery.]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[37a7ee64da2886fddb3d8653f4523dd2.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[326]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[KERR,]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[William Ireland (Bill)]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2016-06-26 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[1969-12-31 19:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:13:52]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:13:52]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[William Ireland (Bill) KERR
KERR, William Ireland (Bill) After a short but courageous battle with cancer, passed away at sunrise June 26, 2016, surrounded by his loving family. Survived by his wife of 43 years Anne, sons Matthew (Kristen) and Robert (Laura). Sister Ann Tait (Bob). Cremation has taken place, Celebration of Life to take place at a later date. In lieu of flowers, donations to your favourite charity would be appreciated.]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[bca32d4b65e7d7d1eec784e069f438c9.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[328]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[MacMILLAN,]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[Madeline]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2016-06-23 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[1969-12-31 19:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:15:17]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:15:17]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[Madeline MacMILLAN
MacMILLAN, Madeline Died suddenly at Hamilton General on Thursday, June 23, 2016. Beloved wife of Earl MacMillan. Beloved mother of Suzanne of Calgary and Joanne of Hamilton. Beloved mother-in-law of Mark Gamble of Calgary. Great-grandmother of Robbie and Jennifer of Hamilton, Marcus Gamble of Calgary, Cooper of Hamilton and Violet Gamble of Calgary. In lieu of flowers, donations to Sam Aphasia Program in Hamilton.]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[55c8aa663fcd83644677335b27d01970.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[329]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[PALOMBO,]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[Giuseppe "Joe"]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2016-06-28 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[1969-12-31 19:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:15:54]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:15:54]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[Giuseppe "Joe" PALOMBO
PALOMBO, Giuseppe "Joe" Passed away suddenly on June 28, 2016. Loving husband to Eva. Guiding father to Joey and Pasquale and stepfather to Jay (Shirley) and Jennifer (Danny). Nonno to 6 grandchildren. Joe will also be missed by many other family and friends. Visitation at Bay Gardens Funeral Home - "William J. Markey Chapel", 947 Rymal Road East, HAMILTON (905.574.0405) on Friday from 1-5 p.m. Vigil at 4:30 p.m. Funeral Mass will be held at Our Lady of the Assumption Parish, Stoney Creek on Saturday, July 2, 2016 at 10:00 a.m. Burial to follow at Our Lady of The Angels Catholic Cemetery, Stoney Creek. For those who wish, memorial donations made to Our Lady of the Assumption Parish would be appreciated. Please sign the online Book of Condolences at www.baygardens.ca]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[97623543e23010d77dc0aadd12fcc5b8.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[330]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[QUAGLIA,]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[John (F.G.)]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2016-06-28 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[1969-12-31 19:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:16:41]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:16:41]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[John (F.G.) QUAGLIA
QUAGLIA, John (F.G.) John passed away peacefully on Tuesday, June 28, 2016 at St. Joseph's Hospital with his wife and son by his side at the age of 77 years old. Beloved husband of Anna and beloved father of Robert. Cherished son of the late Tullio and Antonina Quaglia. Brother-in-law of Leda and the late Italo Speranza, Mary and the late Jim Parsons and the late Luisa and Robert Langley. A sincere thank you to all the staff at St. Joseph's Hospital for their compassionate care for John. Visitation at FRISCOLANTI FUNERAL CHAPEL (43 Barton Street East) on Wednesday, June 29 from 2-4 p.m. and 6-9 p.m. with Vigil prayers at 3:30 p.m. A Funeral Mass will be celebrated at St. Anthony of Padua Church, (830 Barton Street East) on Thursday, June 30, 2016 at 10:30 a.m. Interment to follow at Hutcheson Memorial Cemetery, Hunstville at a later date. If you ask the Father for anything in My name, He will give it to you … Ask, and you will receive. - The Gospel of John 16:23-24. Heavenly Father, thank You for the great gift of a great man who loved his wife and son dearly and who always gave generously of his love to others without counting the cost. In your name JESUS, Amen.]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[90f9f2051cb48d615d789e2c944a1d00.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[331]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[SAMPSON,]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[Brett Francis Drake]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2016-06-26 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[1969-12-31 19:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:17:27]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:17:27]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[Brett Francis Drake SAMPSON
SAMPSON, Brett Francis Drake 1965-2016 It is with sadness and heartbreak that we announce the passing away of Brett Sampson, age 51, on the morning of Sunday, June 26, 2016. He died peacefully in his home surrounded by his family after a long battle with cancer. He leaves behind his loving wife and best friend of 30 years, Kim Townsend, and 3 adoring daughters, Brooke (16), Charlotte (14), and Tess Sampson (12). He will be sorely missed by his mother and father, Kerstin and John Sampson; his sister and brother, Olivia and Peter Sampson; his father-in-law Brooke Townsend and wife Irene Townsend and mother-in-law Anne Townsend and husband Uwe Schaub; his brothers-in-law, Erol Girt, Kirkby Townsend , and Trevor Townsend; and his sisters-in-law , Deborah Townsend, Anna Robertson and Dawn Peel . He will be fondly remembered as Uncle Brett by his many nieces and nephews - Mirha and Sabine Girt, Johnny, Noel, and Kate Sampson; Jason and Megan Townsend; Andrew and Michael Dudley; Kirk, Annie, Rory, Jack and Perry Townsend; and step niece and nephew Emily Lindsey Ballantine and Tyler Garvey. Brett was born on February 12, 1965 in Toronto where he spent his early childhood before moving to Montreal in his teens. He completed his B.A.H. in Economics at Queen's University in 1989 and then spent the next couple of years travelling throughout Asia and working in a UN Cambodian Refugee camp in Thailand. Upon his return, he completed his Masters of Business at Queen's University, started his family, and built his lifelong career in the printing industry. Brett will be remembered by his selfless nature, compassionate soul, adventurous spirit, and profound integrity. Brett was a person who made the world a better place. His big smile could light up any room and his love of learning never ceased. He had many passions including canoe tripping, cycling, skiing, 'fixing things', reading, gardening, and anything to do with airplanes. Brett was also an accomplished pianist and pilot. One of his greatest accomplishments was in being a 'hand's-on' father for his 3 beautiful daughters. They will be his greatest legacy. A big thank you to the many doctors and medical personal at Sunnybrook Hospital and the Juravinski Cancer Centre, and to the nurses who visited daily at our home through CCAC and St. Joseph's Healthcare in Hamilton. There will be a Celebration of Life on Thursday, June 30th at 4:30. It will be held in the Artsplex at Hillfield Strathallan College at 299 Fennel Avenue West, Hamilton, Ontario L9C 1G3. For online memorial information please visit www.basicfunerals.ca/obituaries. In lieu of flowers, family and friends wishing to honour Brett can contribute to Doctors Without Borders: https://msf.donorportal.ca/Donation/InHonour.aspx?L=en-CA&G=190&F=1222&T=INHON or to The Brett Sampson Senior School Memorial Award at Hillfield Strathallan College, an award that will support a senior student who is creative, innovative and passionate about business studies: https://hsc.on.ca/donatetoday If you have any questions please feel free to call our life long family friend, Stephanie Michelle, at 905-730-9709.]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[5aa620e1d11a3b482117f7003ea6a3a5.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[332]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[SKUSE,]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[Josephine]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2016-06-27 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[1969-12-31 19:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:18:15]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:18:15]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[Josephine SKUSE
SKUSE, Josephine It is with great sadness we announce the peaceful passing of our mother, Josephine on June 27, 2016 in her 82nd year. Reunited once again with her beloved husband Ken. Survived by her children Danny (Chris), David (Linda), Denise Pye (Gary), Darrell (Diane), Doug (Holly). Proud grandmother of Rebecca, Katie, Alexandra, Amanda, Stewart, Daryl, Daniel, Nicole, Dalton and Dylan. She will be missed by her dear brother Ray Baker (Elaine), nieces Alanna, Adrienne, Cheryl, Elaine and nephews David and Ron, predeceased by her sisters Cecile Bogue (Ross), Jean Wells (Verne). Josie will always be remembered for her charisma and stellar smile. She leaves behind many life-long friends. Family and friends are welcomed to join us in a celebration of life on Thursday, June 30th from 3-7 p.m. at 260 Westbank Trail, Stoney Creek. 'Those we hold dear never truly leave us. They live on in the kindness they showed, the comfort they shared and the love they brought into our lives.']]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[040115c0d96a62a40375f24831fa5099.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[333]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[TUPPER,]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[Gary]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2016-06-27 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[1969-12-31 19:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:18:52]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:18:52]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[Gary TUPPER
TUPPER, Gary Gary Tupper, 73, peacefully passed away on Monday, June 27, 2016. Loving husband to the late Karen and loving father of Cheryl (Stephen) and Brad (Andrea). Will be missed by his grandchildren, Jaden, Ella, Keira and Natalie. He was a beloved brother (Wendy), brother-in-law, uncle and friend. A thank you to the staff of Maple Villa. Cremation has taken place and a burial service will be held at Burlington Memorial Gardens on Thursday, June 30th at 11 a.m.]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[990b33158c064fcbfde3bde8ac25acd0.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[334]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[WALLACE,]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[Agnes F.]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2016-06-23 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[1969-12-31 19:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:19:38]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2016-06-30 12:19:38]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[Agnes F. WALLACE
WALLACE, Agnes F. Peacefully at St. Joseph's Hospital on June 23, 2016 in her 97th year. Daughter to the late Samuel Wallace and Sarah Harvey of Newtownards, Ireland. Sister to Esther, Sarah, Robert and Samuel. Loving Aunt to Jim, Sam, Bill, Roy and Bob Hart. Beloved Great-Aunt to Michael, Carla, David, Gary, Paul, Bruce, Andrea, Patricia, Brian and Lee. A very special Great-Great-Aunt to Dallas, Sydney, Savana, Dakota, Jeffrey, Stephanie, Shannon, Amanda, Mallorie, Kelsey, Gillian, Dana, Geoff, Lisa, Natalie, Jesse, Kasia, Amanda, Shannon and Brendan. An adoring Great-Great-Great-Aunt to Stefano and Silvana. Agnes was also loved and will be dearly missed by the members of her extended family Mary, Florence, Ruth, Barb, Joan, Lori, Kim, Bobby, Francesse, Sonia, Debbie, Mike, Aline, Les, Natalie, Daryl, Iuly, John and Laurent. Agnes maintained regular contact over the years with many of her relatives in Ireland; all of whom she loved dearly. Friends will be received at DONALD V. BROWN FUNERAL HOME , 36 Lake Ave. Dr., Stoney Creek on Thursday, July 7, 2016 from 10 a.m. until the time of funeral service in the Funeral Home Chapel at 11 a.m. Interment to follow at Woodland Cemetery. Notes of sympathy and condolence may be made at www.donaldvbrown.ca]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[0100c230587f7bb2739735156ae692df.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[5765]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[RUTH]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[MASUYE (TOYOTA) ABE]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[1936-12-14 00:00:00]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2017-06-07 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[2017-06-16 00:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2017-06-12 08:55:06]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2017-06-12 08:55:06]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[RUTH MASUYE ABE (nee TOYOTA) December 14, 1936 - June 7, 2017 Born in Duncan, BC, to the late Shoshichi and Kiriye Toyota, Ruth passed away peacefully on Wednesday, June 7, 2017, at the age of 80. Despite having cancer for the last few months, with grace and dignity she was able to enjoy the company of friends and family in her home. Beloved wife of the late Kenneth Kiyokazu Abe (2012) for 52 years and cherished mother to Lois Glendenning (Rick), Michael (Izumi), Suzanne Moriya (Hiroshi) and Glenn (Susan). Proud grandmother to Brandon (Sandy), Tyler, Rachel, Kento, Natsuki, Akira, Megan and Callum. She will also be dearly missed by her sisters, Sugar, Katy, Minnie and May and brothers Bob and Bill. Predeceased by brothers Mas, Yosh, Mus, Tomekichi, Jim, George and Roy. She will be remembered for her kind heart, gentle soul and beautiful smile and dimples. She was a devoted wife, mother, grandmother, sister, aunt and friend to all whose lives she touched. Ruth graduated from the University of Western Ontario with the Victorian Order of Nurses' Class of 1958 and stayed in touch with her classmates and enjoyed regular reunions. Ruth had many talents and hobbies. Her beautiful cakes appear in family photo albums of many of those who knew her. She also loved bunka, gardening, lawn bowling, puzzles and crosswords. Like Ken, she too enjoyed the occasional visit to the "ii toko". The family would like to express its gratitude to Dr. Duncan and to Drs. Nahji, Comay, Phillips, Strang and Plach, nurses and staff at the Cancer Clinic and ER/5S at Joseph Brant Hospital, CCAC home care staff and The Carpenter Hospice. Visitation at SMITH'S FUNERAL HOME, 1167 Guelph Line, (one stoplight north of QEW), Burlington, on Friday, June 16, 2017 from 3-5 and 7-9 p.m. Funeral Service will take place in the Chapel on Saturday, June 17, 2017 at 10:30 a.m. Reception to follow. In lieu of flowers and koden, please consider a donation to The Carpenter Hospice, 2250 Parkway Drive, Burlington, ON L7P 1T1. www.smithsfh.com ]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[d56e9888496a9be5cf45a61ea552e6c9.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[0]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[5795]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[Arnolda]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[Willemina BEEKENKAMP (nee Van Wely)]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2017-06-10 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[2017-06-14 00:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2017-06-12 10:26:49]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2017-06-12 10:26:49]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[Arnolda Willemina BEEKENKAMP (nee Van Wely)
BEEKENKAMP, Arnolda Willemina (nee Van Wely) "He makes me lie down in green pastures, He leads me beside quiet waters, He restores my soul." Psalm 23 Passed to be with her Lord on Saturday, June 10, 2017 at Shalom Manor, Grimsby at the age of 98. Cherished wife to the late Jacob Beekenkamp. Beloved Moe to Alice Tigchelaar. Loving Oma to Alexander, Jennifer, and Matthew (Nicole). Great Oma to Addison. Arnolda was a proud sister to Bill (Audrey) Van Wely, Johanna Van Wely, the late Carla (Arie) Koornneef, and the late Jean (Bill) Muysson. Arnolda will also be missed by many nieces and nephews. Many thanks to Alice Dobler, Helen Hagen, Kathy Kralt, Jeanetta Knight, Nella Sandrock, and Arnolda's care teams at Blackadar, Shalom Manor, and the VON. Friends will be received at the DONALD V. BROWN FUNERAL HOME , 36 Lake Avenue Drive, Stoney Creek on Wednesday from 3-5 and 7-9 p.m. A private family interment will be held. Funeral Service to be held on Thursday June 15, 2017 at 11 a.m. at First Hamilton Christian Reformed Church, 181 Charlton Avenue West, Hamilton. In lieu of flowers, donations to First Hamilton Christian Reformed Church or the Arthritis Society of Canada would be appreciated. Online condolences may be left at www.donaldvbrown.ca]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[893ce211d76d2e0d2b9e7611102ab8cd.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
	<node>
		<column_1><![CDATA[6066]]></column_1>
		<column_2><![CDATA[Thomas]]></column_2>
		<column_3><![CDATA[Patrick DALY]]></column_3>
		<column_4><![CDATA[1969-12-31 00:00:00]]></column_4>
		<column_5><![CDATA[2017-06-17 00:00:00]]></column_5>
		<column_6><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_6>
		<column_7><![CDATA[1969-12-31 19:00:00]]></column_7>
		<column_8><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_8>
		<column_9><![CDATA[9]]></column_9>
		<column_10><![CDATA[2017-06-22 11:08:03]]></column_10>
		<column_11><![CDATA[2017-06-22 11:08:03]]></column_11>
		<column_12><![CDATA[0]]></column_12>
		<column_13><![CDATA[DALY, Thomas Patrick July 7, 1929 - June 17, 2017 Born in New York City and raised there and in Ireland, Tom learned at an early age to become independent and self-reliant. While working in Bermuda he met and married the love of his life Joan (nee Lapp), eventually returning to her hometown Hamilton. The call of his roots later brought them to Ireland to witness and record 'The Troubles'. A skilled professional photographer with The Spectator and later St. Joseph's Hospital, Tom saw and captured life with clarity and compassion. He is predeceased by Joan, his parents, and most of his immediate family members, but lives on in the hearts and minds of all who knew him, especially generations of nieces and nephews. The family plans a private celebration of his life but would like to thank all of the dedicated people who provided health care for his many medical events, with special thanks to the teams at St. Joseph's and the Hamilton General. Tom was a unique individual with a gentle, quiet manner. He was deeply treasured and we will all miss his wisdom, humanity and humour. To honour this thoughtful, generous and modest man, consider a donation to the Education charity of your choice.]]></column_13>
		<column_14><![CDATA[1]]></column_14>
		<column_15><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_15>
		<column_16><![CDATA[aad11e37230d05dddf66471287242d92.jpg]]></column_16>
		<column_17><![CDATA[9]]></column_17>
		<column_18><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_18>
		<column_19><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_19>
		<column_20><![CDATA[NULL]]></column_20>
		<column_21><![CDATA[0]]></column_21>
		<column_22><![CDATA[1]]></column_22>
		<column_23><![CDATA[0]]></column_23>
		<column_24><![CDATA[9]]></column_24>
		<column_25><![CDATA[Hamilton]]></column_25>
		<column_26><![CDATA[9]]></column_26>
		<column_27><![CDATA[0]]></column_27>
		<column_28><![CDATA[0]]></column_28>
		<column_29><![CDATA[http://rss.cbc.ca/lineup/canada-hamiltonnews.xml]]></column_29>
	</node>
</data>
